# THE ANGELS HAVE GONE #.
# THE SONGS HAVE GONE SILENT #.
# YOU'RE SINKING LIKE A STONE #.
# BEFORE THE TIDE #.
# THE RIVER RUNS CO-O-LD #.
# THE FIGHT IS OVER #.
# STILL THE HAUNTED.
RUINS OF NIGHT #.
# CALL YOUR NAME #.
MM-HMM.
YES.
INTO THE UNKNOWN.
GOODBYE!
THANK YOU, OLD LADY DANIELS.
GOODBYE, GREGORY.
AND PLEASE DON'T CALL ME OLD LADY.
YES, SIR, YOUNG MAN!
HEY, WIRT, WHATCHA DOING?
NOTHING.
I WAS HELPING OLD LADY DANIELS RAKE SOME LEAVES
IN EXCHANGE FOR CANDY.
GREG, IT'S HALLOWEEN.
CANDY IS FREE.
OLD LADY DANIELS SAYS NOTHING
IN THIS WORLD IS FREE.
OH, HEY, AND LOOK!
I ALSO GOT THIS ROCK.
HEY, WIRT,
WANNA LEARN SOME ROCK FACTS?
SO, YOU WANT TO GO LOOK FOR FROGS WITH ME
LIKE YOU SAID YOU WOULD AWHILE AGO
AND HAVEN'T DONE IT YET?
NAH. NAH, I'M BUSY.
IS THAT BEE NAMED SARA?
W-WHAT?
YOUR TAPE SAYS "FOR SARA."
ARE YOU GONNA GIVE IT TO
SARA THE BEE?
I-I WANT TO, BUT...
I CAN'T.
CAN I SEE IT?
YEAH. IT'S JUST A TAPE.
HMM. YEAH. OKAY,
I'LL GIVE IT TO HER FOR YOU.
OH, GREG! W-WAIT! NO, NO!
OH, LOOK AT YOU.
WHAT ARE YOU SUPPOSED TO BE?
IT'S AN ELEPHANT COSTUME.
BRRRH, BRRRH... PBHT!
SEE MY TRUNK?
YEAH THAT'S... CUTE.
I'M AN EGG!
YEAH, EVERYBODY KNOWS YOU'RE AN EGG, RHONDI.
SHUT IT, KATHLEEN.
WHATEVER.
SO, WHAT ARE YOU, WIRT?
SOME KIND OF GNOME?
UH, I D... I DON'T KNOW.
WELL, IT'S ... SEE, I WAS ...
I THOUGHT I'D JUST, LIKE...
HEY! WHAT'S THIS!
THAT'S WIRT'S TAPE FOR SARA.
OOH! WIRT LOVES SARA!
YOU WANT US TO GIVE IT TO HER?
UH, IT'S FOR A DIFFERENT SARA...
NOT THE ONE YOU'RE THINKING ABOUT.
YEAH, WIRT'S TALKING ABOUT
MASCOT SARA...
THE ONE HE'S BEEN LOOKING AT ALL NIGHT.
WHA...?!
OOH! WIRT'S GOT A CRUSH ON SARA.
HA, HA, HA! AHA, HA, HA!
WELL, YOU BETTER ACT FAST 'CAUSE WE HEARD
JASON FUNDERBERKER IS GONNA ASK HER OUT AT THE HALLOWEEN PARTY TONIGHT.
JASON FUNDERBERKER?
- YEAH!
...YEAH.
WHAT I.. BUT.. BUT, UM...
YOU OKAY, WIRT?
YEAH! EVERYTHING'S...
EVERYTHING'S JASON FUNDERBERKER.
- WHAT?
UH, UH...
JASON FUNDERBERKER,
I-I GOT TO GO.
BYE!
IS THE DOVE NEVER TO MEET THE SEA
FOR WANT OF THE ODIOUS MOUNTAIN?
HEY, SO...
FROG HUNT?
HUH?
I KEEP HEARING RIBBITING AROUND TOWN,
AND I THINK IT'S
THE LAST FROG OF THE SEASON.
NO, I JUST WANT TO WALLOW IN MISERY.
SARA AND JASON FUNDERBERKER. UGH.
THAT GUY'S GOT HIS ACT TOGETHER.
HE'S THE TOTAL PACKAGE. I CAN'T COMPETE.
YOU'RE THE TOTAL PACKAGE, TOO, WIRT.
I BET SHE'LL REALLY LIKE YOUR TAPE.
HUH! WE NEVER GOT THE TAPE BACK!
I CAN'T LET HER HEAR THAT TAPE!
WHY NOT?
THAT TAPE HAS GOT POETRY AND CLARINET ON IT, GREG.
POETRY AND CLARINET!
SARA AND JASON
FUNDERBERKER ARE GONNA START DATING,
AND THEN THEY'LL HEAR THAT TAPE,
AND THEN THEY'LL JUST SIT AND LISTEN TO IT
AND LAUGH AND LAUGH AND LAUGH AND LAUGH.
WHY DON'T YOU ASK SARA OUT FIRST?
THAT WAY-
NO, NO! UGH!
WHY DID YOU HAVE TO TAKE THE TAPE?
MY LIFE IS CRUMBLING ALL AROUND ME!
OKAY, I THINK WE SHOULD PUT OUR FROG HUNT ON HOLD
AND GO GET THAT TAPE BACK.
GUYS, WHERE'S THE TAPE?
WE PUT IT IN SARA'S JACKET FOR YOU.
YOU BETTER HURRY. SHE'S CHANGING IN THE TRACK SHACK.
'SCUSE ME.
WUH-OH!
THE JACKET!
HEY! ARE YOU TRYING TO SPY ON SARA?
UH... NO.
RUN, GREG!
HEY, SARA, BE CAREFUL, HUH?
THERE'S SOME REAL CREEPS OUT THERE TONIGHT.
THANKS, JIMMY.
HEY, YOU TWO ROBBERS,
YOU'RE UNDER ARREST.
NAH, I'M JUST KIDDING. HAPPY HALLOWEEN.
HEY, STOP RUNNING IN THE STREET!
JUST KIDDING. HAPPY HALLOWEEN.
THERE SHE GOES. LET'S GET HER.
YEAH, LET'S GET HER.
NO, W-WE'RE NOT GONNA GET HER LIKE THAT.
WHAT ARE WE DOING?
WE'RE JUST GONNA GET THE TAPE BACK.
OH, YEAH!
LET'S GO IN AFTER HER.
HUH... I CAN'T.
I WASN'T INVITED TO THIS PARTY.
I'LL GO IN!
YOU WEREN'T INVITED EITHER.
OH.
YEAH, MAN, THERE'S LOTS OF.
BAT-AND-BALL GAMES BESIDES BASEBALL
...ONE OLD CAT, TWO OLD CAT, STOOLBALL, ROUNDBALL...
WHY ARE YOU TALKING TO THEM?
OH. HEY...GUYS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HE SAID, BUT I-IT WASN'T TRUE.
- OH, HEY, WIRT.
- HOW'S IT GOING?
HI, WIRT!
OH. UH, YEAH.
WELL, SEE YOU AROUND, GUYS.
I USED TO BE REALLY GOOD AT BALLET,
BUT MY MOM WANTED ME TO BE A WRESTLER.
OH, WIRT. YOU'RE HERE.
WELL, I...
I WAS JUST ASKING IF YOU WERE HERE.
OH, WOW.
OH, HEY, WE'RE GONNA
GO TO THE GRAVEYARD.
OH. ARE YOU GONNA...
DO SOMETHING THERE?
NAH, WE'RE JUST GONNA HANG OUT
AND DRINK AGE-APPROPRIATE DRINKS.
- LIKE JUICE?
- YEAH, WHATEVER.
AGE-APPROPRIATE STUFF THAT'S NOT ILLEGAL.
HEY, YOU SHOULD COME.
UH, I DON'T ...
HEY, SARA.
ARE YOU READY TO GO?
HEY, JASON FUNDERBERKER.
OH, HEY, WIRT.
LET'S GO, SARA.
YOU COMING, WIRT?
NO, NO. YOU... YOU GO...
HAVE FUN WITH JASON FUNDERBERKER.
OKAY.
BUT IF YOU WANT TO STOP BYE LATER OR SOMETHING...
MM. BYE, WIRT.
SAYONARA, JASON FUNDERBERKER.
HUH!
SARA'S JACKET!
MY JACKET! THANKS, WIRT.
WELL, SEE YA ... HOPEFULLY.
BYE.
YOU'RE LIMITING THE UNIVERSE.
TO ONLY THINGS HUMANS.
COULD UNDERSTAND.
WELL, YOU'RE LIMITING THE UNIVERSE.
BY LIMITING THE POSSIBILITY.
OF HUMAN UNDERSTANDING.
OH, YEAH. MAYBE.
SARA.
YEAH?
DO YOU BELIEVE IN...
GHOSTS?
WHY?
CAUSE THERE'S ONE RIGHT BEHIND YOU!
AW, I'M JUST KIDDING.
IT'S OKAY, FUNDERBERKER.
STOP! YOU HIT ME!
COME ON.
GRAAWR.
WIRT, YOU TRICKED ME!
I DIDN'T KNOW THIS WAS A FROG HUNT ALL ALONG.
IT NEVER WAS A...
HUH!
A WITCHES GATHERING!
A GUY WITH AN AXE SHOWED UP!
UGH.
EVERYBODY LOVES FUNDERBERKER.
WHAT DO I DO?
I'LL PRETEND TO BE A DEAD ELEPHANT
AND DISTRACT THEM WHILE YOU GET THE TAPE.
PLEASE JUST STAY HERE.
AND SO SHE KEPT GETTING CLOSER...
AND CLOSER...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?.
- JASON, HEHE
- HEHE
OH, JASON...
GO, GREG. DO IT.
OKAY.
UH... YOU CAN LET GO OF OF MY HAND NOW.
OH... YEAH.
YOU COULD HOLD MY HAND, FUNDERBERKER. I DON'T CARE.
WOOOOOOOH,
WAH WAH WAH!
HEY, ISN'T THAT WIRT'S LITTLE BROTHER?
NOOOOO,
I AM THE HEADLESS ELEPHANT!
IS WIRT HERE, TOO?
OVER THERE!
THERE HE IS.
WIRT, WE CAN SEE YOU, MAN.
OH. HEY, GUYS.
GREG! THERE YOU ARE.
TOTALLY WASN'T SPYING ON ANYBODY.
I WAS JUST LOOKING FOR ...
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?.
HUH!
IS THIS SOME KIND OF
WITCHES' GATHERING?
YOU'RE ALL UNDER ARREST.
RUN!
HEY, HEY! I WAS JUST KIDDING.
SLOW DOWN, KIDS.
YOU'RE GONNA TRIP OR SOMETHING.
RUN, RUN, RUN!
WHERE DO WE GO?
THAT WAY!
GREG! WHY DID YOU SAY THIS WAY?
I THOUGHT I HEARD A FROG.
THIS IS PRIVATE PROPERTY.
UH...
HEY, DON'T CLIMB UP THERE.
THAT'S DANGEROUS!
GET DOWN HERE BEFORE.
YOU HURT YOURSELF!
HUH?
IT HAS MY NAME ON IT.
LET'S GO LISTEN TO IT.
NOOOOOOO!
KIDS, REALLY, GET DOWN FROM
THAT WALL.
THAT'S IT. THAT'S THE END.
NO, DARN IT. NO.
I MEAN COME DOWN THIS WAY.
ONCE AGAIN, YOU RUIN MY LIFE.
WHO? ME?
UGH! YOU AND YOUR STUPID DAD!
YOU'RE ALWAYS PRODDING ME,
TRYING TO GET ME TO JOIN
MARCHING BAND.
OH, YEAH!
IF YOU JOIN THE MARCHING BAND,
YOU COULD HANG OUT WITH SARA MORE!
THAT SHIP HAS SAILED, GREG.
THANKS TO YOU MESSING THAT UP, TOO.
GRAAWR.
HOLD THAT THOUGHT, WIRT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING NOW?
HAHA! WE FOUND OUR LUCKY FROG.
WE GOT TO NAME HIM FOR GOOD LUCK.
I DON'T WANT TO HAVE ANYTHING TO DO WITH YOU OR THAT FROG!
OKAY, I'LL TRY TO THINK OF A NAME MYSELF.
UGH. I'M LEAVING.
HMM?
HUH?
# THERE'S AN OLD BLACK TRAIN
A-COMIN' #.
# SCRAPING 'LONG THE IRON #.
# YOU DON'T NEED NO TICKET, BOYS #.
# IT'LL TAKE YOU IN IT'S TIME #.
Huh?
Where... Huh?
Oh. You're awake.
Here, eat some dirt.
Uh, Beatrice?
You know my daughter!
Where is she?
I don't know.
Graaaaawr
Somebody left you and that frog on the doorstep.
Beatrice.
But...
have you seen my brother?
No, I'm sorry.
Uh, I gotta go!
You're in no shape to head into that snowstorm, young man.
Here, here, eat more dirt.
Thanks.
Come on, guy.
Let's go find Greg.
At least wait until the
storm dies down a bit.
You'll be no good to your brother dead.
I was never any good
to him alive, either.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
If you see Beatrice again,
give her a hug for us.
Yeah.